viagogo.co.uk 2013-05-07

# 

## Privacy Policy

Your privacy is very important to us. We understand you want to remain in control of your personal information and that we must earn and retain your trust. viagogo has created this privacy statement to show our commitment to the privacy of any personal details that you provide us when using our web site. We can assure you that we keep your information confidential and do not sell or rent our customers' personal information to third parties. 

Please review this Privacy Policy, which sets out our policies regarding the collection, utilization and protection of the personal information of those using viagogo. Personal information includes information that is attributable to a specific individual, such as name, address, telephone number, email address and credit card number. **When using our web site, you are consenting to the practices set forth in this Privacy Policy.**

Please note that when browsing our site, the provision of any personal information is not required unless and until you choose to make a purchase or sign up for one of our email newsletters or other services as described below. Children (persons under the age of 18) are not eligible to use the Site unsupervised and we ask that children do not submit any personal information to us. If you are under the age of 18, you may only use this Site in conjunction with and under the supervision of your parents or guardians. 

Making a Purchase

In order to purchase tickets and related services through our site, essential personal information such as your name, your telephone number, your email address, and any additional information required for authenticating a purchase is required. If you are purchasing multiple tickets or buying tickets on behalf of others, please ensure that each of these other customers agrees, in advance, to disclosure of their personal information to us. 

If you purchase ticket(s), your name and address may be provided to another user for the sole purpose of delivering the specific purchased product(s). The other user agrees to not use this information for any other purpose, either in connection with such shipment(s) or separately from such shipment(s). The other user also agrees not to separately contact you at any time for any reason. 

Information you provide may also be provided to our partners to verify your compliance with any special conditions which might apply

Customer Registration

If you choose to become a registered customer of viagogo, you must provide us with your name, address, telephone number, email address, a unique login name, password, password validation, and a password hint to help you to recall your password. This information is collected on the registration form for various reasons including: (i) for your personal identification; (ii) to complete reservations; (iii) to enable us and our partners to contact you for customer service purposes; (iv) to tailor the content of our site to meet our customer’s needs; (v) to share certain information with selected partners; (vi) to make any necessary product improvements to our site and (vii) to permit us or our partners to verify your compliance with any special conditions which might apply. Please note that we do request your email address to confirm your new client registration and each time you purchase a ticket via our web site. 

For your convenience, you may prefer to create an online customer profile by providing us with details of events that may interest you, payment and billing information, delivery address, and/or other personal information. This information will be used to assist you in purchasing tickets more efficiently.

Sharing of information with partners

viagogo may share your personal information (excluding credit or bank card details) with certain selected viagogo partners if you register or transact with viagogo including when you do so on a co-branded partner site. 

If you opt in, these partners may use your personal information to contact you regarding related sites which they think may be of interest to you as a viagogo customer. 

These partners will be based worldwide and by agreeing to this privacy policy, you are consenting to the transfer of your personal data to these selected partners regardless of where they are based. 

Automatic Logging of Session Data

Generic information about your computer's connection to the Internet, called "session data", will automatically be logged. This information is anonymous and can not be used to track your personal information. Session data consists of things such as IP address, operating system and type of browser software being used and the activities conducted by the user while on our site. An IP address is a number that enables computers attached to the Internet, such as our web servers, to know where to send data back to the user, such as the pages of the site the user wishes to view. We collect session data because it helps us administer our web site, track correlative information and to collate statistics in relation to visitor traffic. We may use your IP address to help us diagnose problems with our server. Rest assured that this information can not be linked to you personally. 

Cookies

A cookie is a small file of information that is automatically stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive when you enter our web site. Cookies can only identify your computer and not the individual user, by storing some basic information which will enable us to identify if you have previously visited our web site. Cookies are only read by the server that placed them, and are unable to do such things as run programs on your computer, plant viruses, or harvest your personal information. The use of cookies is very common and viagogo's use of cookies is similar to that of other reputable online companies. 

Any personal information that you provide us with such as your name and address etc. is neither gathered nor stored in the cookies placed by the viagogo web site and, as a result, your information will not be passed on to any third parties. 

Most web browsers automatically accept cookies but it is possible to change the options on your web browser or use certain software programs, which will enable you to control how and whether cookies will be accepted by your browser. You can disable cookies or set your browser to alert you when cookies are being sent. viagogo supports your right to block any unwanted Internet activity, especially that of unscrupulous websites, but please note that if you choose to block viagogo cookies, this may disable certain features on our site and may make it impossible to purchase or use certain services available on the site. It is possible however to block cookie activity from certain web sites while permitting cookies from sites you trust, like viagogo. 

Opting Out

As a viagogo customer, you may opt in at any time to occasionally receive updates from us about ticket sales in your area, special offers, new viagogo services, and other items that may be of interest to you via email, text messages, phone or post. Where previous indication of consent has been provided, it is possible for you to opt out at any time, in order to no longer receive these types of messages either through an opt out feature in the message or through your account settings. Your account settings are accessible on the viagogo home page. 

If you opt in, viagogo's partners may sell, rent or trade personal information (excluding credit or bank card details) to certain third parties. If you do not wish viagogo's partners to pass on these details, please do not opt in, or if you have already opted in, use the opt out procedure as described in above paragraph. 

Our Security Precautions

Our web site has security features in place to protect against loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. All personal information you provide to viagogo is transmitted using 128 bit Secure Server Software SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encryption. SSL is a proven coding system that allows your browser to automatically encrypt, or scramble, all of your personal data before you send it to us. It will not therefore be possible for your payment method data, name and address to be read as the information travels over the Internet. In addition, whenever you transact on viagogo, you are protected by viagogo’s guarantee. 

Disclosure of Information

We do not sell, rent or trade your personal information to third parties for marketing purposes without your express consent. 

Third Party Vendors and their Privacy Policies

viagogo may contain links to other web sites for which we are not responsible. By clicking on any such links, you are entering another web site which will contain content and practices for which viagogo has no responsibility. We therefore encourage you to read the privacy statements of all such sites independently as their policies may be materially different from this Privacy Policy. Please note that it is your responsibility to maintain the secrecy of your passwords and your viagogo membership account information. Please be vigilant with this information, especially whenever you are online. 

We may use third-party advertising companies, to serve or track ads on our web site and other web sites. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other web sites in order to measure advertising effectiveness and to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you. 

Transfer of Your Personal Information and Financial Information Outside of the EEA

Please note that from time to time, viagogo may transfer your personal and/or financial information to other companies in order to perform or improve our services or to help our security, credit risk or fraud protection activities. As mentioned, elsewhere in this privacy policy we may also send personal information to our partners. By submitting to us your details, you are providing consent to the transfer of your information for the purposes set out in this paragraph. Any transfer of information will take place in accordance with this Privacy Policy and as permitted by law.

Transfer of Personal Information in Event of Sale of viagogo or its Assets

In the event that viagogo is sold, or transferred some of its assets to another party, our customer information will most likely also be transferred in connection with such acquisition. If your personal information is transferred, use of such information would remain subject to this Privacy Policy. Your personal information will be passed on to a successor in interest in the event of a liquidation or administration of viagogo.

Disclosure in Compliance with Laws

You should be aware that in addition to the circumstances described above, viagogo may disclose your financial or personal information if required to do so by law, court order, as requested by other government or law enforcement authority, or in the good faith belief that disclosure is otherwise necessary or advisable including, without limitation, to protect the rights or properties of viagogo or its affiliated companies or when we have reason to believe that disclosing the information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing interference with our rights or properties, whether intentionally or otherwise, or when anyone else could be harmed by such activities. 

This policy is effective as of March 19, 2009. Any material changes in the way viagogo uses personal information will be described in future versions of this Privacy Statement. 

You can always submit concerns regarding our Privacy Policy or our privacy practices via email by clicking here. Please reference the privacy policy in your subject line. viagogo will attempt to respond to all reasonable concerns or inquiries within five business days of receipt. You can also write to us at: 

**viagogo**  
Attn: Privacy Team  
viagogo AG, Avenue industrielle 4-6, 1227 Carouge GE, Switzerland 

Thank you for using viagogo! 

## Frequently Asked Questions
